Hey everyone and thanks for jumping back
into the cryptoverse.
Today we're going to talk about Bitcoin.
It's almost crunch time. If you guys
like the content, make sure you
subscribe to the channel, give the video
a thumbs up, and also check out the sale
on into the cryptoverse premium at into
the cryptoverse.com.
As I mentioned a few months ago, we we
do have the direct access option as well
for those wanting something a little bit
more indepth.
Um, Bitcoin is trading at around
$64,000. 6465,000.
And listen guys, I've done this a number
of times before through these midterm
years. And historically, it's always
played out the same way. Bitcoin sells
off
at the very end of the post having year.
No one believes it's the bare market.
Some people start to believe by
February. More people begin to believe
by the summer. But when I say it's
almost crunch time, what I mean is this.
A lot of times Bitcoin will form a low
in the summer, but it's not always it's
not necessarily like the low. It's just
a low. So looking at the summer of 2022,
the summer of 2026, you also have the
summer of 2018. Okay? And then what
happens after that is that there's just
not a lot of volatility. Like Bitcoin
doesn't really do anything. And yes,
there's people talking about could
Bitcoin go back up to 70K, but a lot of
that stuff is irrelevant right now,
right? The point is is that there's just
not a lot of interest in crypto. And it
might feel different than in prior
times, but there's a little secret here.
And when you look at the social
interest, I think a lot of people are
thinking about what it was like back in
2022. But if you look at Bitcoin
in 2026 and look at where the social
interest is, we're at 0.2
four years ago, exactly four years ago,
at the same time in the cycle, social
interest was about 0.5 almost 04 to.5.
So there was more than double the amount
of interest in crypto four years ago
prefttx
than there is now. But in 2018,
in August of 2018, the social risk was
also 0.2. So we've been here before.
Social interest is declining. To a lot
of people, it feels like the cryptoverse
is dying.
But what I'm saying is that it's almost
crunch time. And what happens is you
form a low in the summer, volatility
basically completely dries up. Look at
2018.
Look at 2022.
And then what happens is some event at
the end of the year
causes this final drop.
I can't promise that, right? But that's
what normally happens. And
it wakes everyone back up. One of the
problems I think right now is like, you
know, 60k for, you know, it it seems
like a reasonable price, right? Right? I
mean, given the fact that Bitcoin's
traded a lot above it for a lot of the
last several years, but at the same
time, there's a lot of indicators that
would suggest, hey, you know, you could
go lower, especially if you look at like
the onchain indicators, things like the
MVRVZ score, for example. Uh, that's a
really interesting indicator that shows
you that Bitcoin normally bottoms out
when the MVRVZ score goes below zero.
Hasn't done that yet. There's a few
other metrics like that that you could
argue tell the same thing. So, it's like
there's people that are buying Bitcoin,
right? I've picked some up, but the
point is is like there's still a number
of indicators that haven't really given
the the all clear, if you will. Not that
they have to. I mean, it's always
possible the market just leaves those
indicators behind, but the way it
normally plays out is a low in the
summer, volatility dries up into July,
August, September, and then something
happens
and it wakes everyone back up and it
brings people back and then the next
bull market starts. We are pre that
event in my opinion. We are before that
event. I don't think that that event,
whatever that event is, I don't think
it's happened yet, but I think it's
going to happen relatively soon. It's
almost crunch time. Look, and we've
talked about this for months, how that
Bitcoin would spend time basically
between the 200E moving average and the
bare market resistance band. And what's
going to happen is as the year goes on,
it's going to force a decision at some
point soon. It's going to force this to
to decide what is it actually going to
do. Is it going to break up? Is it going
to break down? I would I mean again I
don't know for sure. I would lean
towards breakdown because that's what it
normally does near the end of midterm
years,
but only time will tell. It's almost
crunch time. It's coming up soon. What I
think though by late November I think
the low will either be in or very very
close to being in
which is why
the ITC conference is in late November.
I think the low could be in October,
could even be late September. Some
circumstances it could be December.
October is the most likely month in my
opinion but that doesn't mean it has to
be.
the conference November 20th through the
22nd with the main day on November 21st.
So, we're doing it late November so that
we can bring everyone together after
theoretically whatever this event is
happens and hopefully we can bring
together some, you know, some more
rational minds to talk about what's
going on in the market. We'd love to
have you guys there. Tickets are going
to go up on September 1st. So, if you've
been planning on going, but you haven't
gotten your ticket yet, I would
encourage you to do so because the
ticket prices will be going up in in
just about um 3 weeks or so. So, make
sure you guys go ahead and get your
ticket. Um and uh I would recommend
doing that relatively soon. And then, as
I've mentioned before as well, uh we've
got a lot of great speakers. We're going
to continue adding speakers. Um, and if
you're not, you know, if you're if
you're not sure um about any of the
logistics, we have some of the details
here on the website, like where you
could stay and whatnot as well. So, make
sure you guys check that out. Link in
the description below.
It's almost crunch time. We got the low
in the summer. We got the low in
February, right? We said low in
February, bounce, low in late June,
early July,
bounce again.
At some point, Bitcoin might be
overstaying its welcome because
remember,
you get the bounce from the low in the
summer,
but in 2018, that balance only lasted
into late July.
In 2022, it lasted into mid August. So,
I don't think Bitcoin is overstate its
welcome just yet at these levels, but
crunch time normally shows up late
August, September, October, right? And
in some cases, it goes all the way into
November, December. Even in in 2015, it
was January. And I mean to speculate
dubiously, you have a low 2015 it was
January. The next one was December. The
next one was November.
extrapolation is dangerous, but if you
were to extrapolate October seems like a
um a Canada month. So again, I know I've
been saying October all year long. I
don't know if it's going to be October.
I think that's the most likely month.
And now that it's only two months away,
French time's almost here. So don't
become complacent. Be aware of what's
happening in the market. And and we'll
see how this shapes up over the next
couple of months. and and hopefully it
does so in a in a manner that is still
resembling other cycles and then
hopefully we can kick that next bull
market off. Again, if you guys like the
content, make sure you subscribe, give
the video a thumbs up, check out the
conference again, September 1st is when
prices are going up and uh also check
out into the cryptoverse premium. I will
see you guys next time. Bye.